Guide to the Rice University Harry Clay Hanszen College Records, 1956-2018 UA 072
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Harry Clay Hanszen College Records
1956-2018
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Hanszen College (Rice University)
UA 072
13 Linear Feet (25 boxes)
0.02 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0072aip_001 (0.02 GB)
0.014 Gigabytes Nearline access: UA0072aip_002 (0.014 GB)
Hanszen College is one of the four original colleges, which were established to house students. The college is named for Harry Clay Hanszen, a wealthy Texas oilman, who served as chairman of Rice's Board of Governors from 1946 to 1950. Formats include Cabinet meeting minutes, correspondence, news clippings, publications, handbooks, videos, brochures and theatrical events programs.
Historical Sketch
Hanszen College is one of the four original colleges, which were established to house students. The college is named for Harry Clay Hanszen, a wealthy Texas oilman, who served as chairman of Rice's Board of Governors from 1946 to 1950.
Scope and Contents
The collection documents the regular business of Rice University's Harry Clay Hanszen College. Formats include Cabinet meeting minutes, correspondence, news clippings, publications, handbooks, videos, brochures and theatrical events programs.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research.
Accruals
Future additions are expected for this material.
Related Papers
See the William H. Masterson Papers, which include a scrapbook made by Hanszen College and Orvetta Masterson's notes for Masters events. See Rice University Archives for records of other Rice University residential colleges. Contact Woodson Research Center staff for assistance.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Social life and customs
Document Types
guidebooks; clippings (information artifacts); calendars; minutes (administrative records)
Subjects (Persons)
Hanszen, Harry Clay
Subjects (Corporations)
Hanszen College (Rice University)
- Series I: Hanszen records, 1956-2006, 35358
  - Subseries I: Hanszen Publications, 160294
    - Handbooks, 1963-1964, 1966, 1973, 1976, 1991, 1993, 1995, n.d.; 160295 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Informational brochures and materials, 160296 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Tenth Annivesary Celebration, Feb. 22, 1967; 160297 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - The Hanszen Voice (1965-1968), 160298 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Liaison (1966-1967), 160299 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Hanszen Tower (1967-1968), 160300 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Hanszen Collage (1974), 160301 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Hanszen: Self-Portrait (1977), 160302 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Events, 1966-1969, n.d.; 160303 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - News clips, 1956, 1967, current; 160304 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Hanszen Music Theatre, 1982, n.d.; 160305 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1964; 160306 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Spring Recital Series, 1965; 160307 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Subseries II: Minutes, Governance, and Events, 160308
    - Cabinet and committee members, 1963-1964, 1966-1967; 160309 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Cabinet meeting minutes and notices, 1967, 1973-1975; 160310 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Cabinet meeting minutes, 1985-1986; 160311 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Cabinet meeting minutes, 1986-1987; 160312 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cabinet meeting minutes, 1987-1997; 160313 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cabinet meeting minutes, 1997-; 160314 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Misc, 1973-1976; 160315 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Cabinet, 1973-1975; 160316 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Newsletters, 1975-1977; 160317 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Programs/Events, 1975-1978; 160318 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Constitution, By-laws, Judicial Code, 1975; 160319 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Calendars, 1973-1976; 160320 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Associates, 1973-1975; 160321 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - "Guidance" in Hanszen College, 1974; 160322 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Masters, 1971-1977; 160323 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Resident Rosters, 1974-1976; 160324 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - O-Week Handbook" "Ferris Bueller's O-Week Off", 2001; 160326 (Box 2, Folder -)
    - Commons reconstruction and refurnishing, 1975; 160325 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - O-Week Handbook: "Snoopy and Co. Week", 2002; 160327 (Box 2, Folder -)
    - O-Week Handbook: "Retr-O Week", 2003; 160328 (Box 2, Folder -)
    - Minutes, 1967-1968; 160329 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1968-1969; 160330 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1970-1971; 160331 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1971-1972; 160332 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1972-1973; 160333 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1973-1974; 160334 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1975-1976; 160335 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1976-1977; 160336 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1977-1978; 160337 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Minutes, 1978-1979; 160338 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Minutes, 1979-1980; 160339 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Minutes, 1980-1981; 160340 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Minutes, 1981-1982; 160341 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Minutes, 1982-1983; 160342 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1983-1984; 160343 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Minutes, 1984-1985; 160344 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Minutes, 1985-1986; 160345 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Minutes, 1987-1988; 160346 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Minutes, 1989-1990; 160347 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Minutes, 1990-1991; 160348 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Minutes, 1991-1992; 160349 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Minutes, 1992-1993; 160350 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Minutes, 1993-1994; 160351 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Minutes, 1994-1995; 160352 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Agenda, minutes, 2003-2004; 160353 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Backpages, Constitution/By-laws changes, and attachments to minutes, 2003-2004; 160354 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Cabinet handouts, attendance sheets, and space requests, 2003-2004; 160355 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Attendance, agenda, minutes, 2004-2005; 160356 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Backpages, handouts, 2004-2005; 160357 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Attendance, agenda, minutes, 2005-2006; 160358 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Backpages, 2005-2006; 160359 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Subseries III: Audio/Visual, 155716
    - Into the Woods, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1992; 155717 (Box 5, Item 1)
    - Into the Woods, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1992; 155718 (Box 5, Item 2)
    - A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1993; 155734 (Box 5, Item 3)
    - West Side Story, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1994; 155735 (Box 5, Item 4)
    - West Side Story, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1994; 155736 (Box 5, Item 5)
    - Fantastics (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1995; 155737 (Box 5, Item 6)
    - Hair, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1996; 155738 (Box 5, Item 7)
    - Hair Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1996; 155739 (Box 5, Item 8)
    - City of Angels, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1997; 155740 (Box 5, Item 9)
    - City of Angels, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1997; 155741 (Box 5, Item 10)
    - Into the Woods, Part I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1999; 155742 (Box 5, Item 11)
    - Into the Woods, Part II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1998; 155743 (Box 5, Item 12)
    - Edloe St. St. Paty Party (8mm Camcorder Tape), March 20, 1999; 155744 (Box 5, Item 13)
    - Guys and Dolls, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 11, 1999; 155745 (Box 5, Item 14)
    - Guys and Dolls, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 11, 1999; 155746 (Box 5, Item 15)
    - Sweet Charity, Part I (8mm Camcorder Tape), October 28, 2000; 155747 (Box 5, Item 16)
    - Sweet Charity, Part II (8mm Camcorder Tape), October 28, 2000; 155748 (Box 5, Item 17)
    - My Fair Lady, Act I (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1, 2002; 155780 (Box 5, Item 18)
    - My Fair Lady, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), November 1, 2002; 155781 (Box 5, Item 19)
    - Kiss Me Kate (8mm Camcorder Tape), October 31, 2003; 155782 (Box 5, Item 20)
    - Kiss Me Kate, Act II (8mm Camcorder Tape), October 31, 2003; 155783 (Box 5, Item 21)
- Series II: Hanszen records, 1998-2012, 159349
  - Backpages, 2011; 159351 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Misc, 159352 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - O-Week, 2011; 159353 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Subseries I: Memorabilia, 2003-2009; 159350
    - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2003; 160360 (Box 7, Item 1)
    - Lego-Week T-Shirt, 2005; 160361 (Box 7, Item 2)
    - Formidable Foe Week T-Shirt, 2006; 160362 (Box 7, Item 3)
    - College Night T-Shirt, Fall 2007; 160363 (Box 7, Item 4)
    - Dynamic DuO-Week T-Shirt, 2007; 160364 (Box 7, Item 5)
    - Cheerio Week T-Shirt, 2008; 160365 (Box 7, Item 6)
    - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2008; 160366 (Box 7, Item 7)
    - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2009; 160367 (Box 7, Item 8)
    - Black Hanszen T-Shirt, 2009; 160368 (Box 7, Item 9)
    - AficionadO-Week T-Shirt, 2009; 160369 (Box 7, Item 10)
    - College Night T-Shirt, Fall 2009; 160370 (Box 7, Item 11)
    - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2010; 160371 (Box 7, Item 12)
    - Black V-Neck T-Shirt, n.d.; 160372 (Box 7, Item 13)
    - 90s College Night T-Shirt, n.d.; 160373 (Box 7, Item 14)
    - Hanszen Prison T-Shirt, n.d.; 160374 (Box 7, Item 15)
    - Gambunta T-Shirt, n.d.; 160375 (Box 7, Item 16)
  - Subseries II: Slides, 1998; 161939
    - Raiders of the Lost O-Week, August 1998; 161940 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Subseries III: News Clips, 161941
    - 2012-, 161942 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Series III: Hanszen records, 1950-2005, 162401
  - Subseries I: Documents, 162404
    - Correspondence, 1992-1997; 162405 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Officers, 1999-2000; 162407 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - O-Week documents, n.d.; 162416 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Indentured servitude contract, 162419 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Subseries II: Publications, 162406
    - Dennis Huston newsclippings, 1978-1990; 162409 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Chustz's Shotz, 1986; 162413 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - The Hanszen Tower, January 1987; 162410 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Notes from the O-Week Coordinators, c. 1989-1992; 162414 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Newsclippings, 1990-2000s; 162411 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Hanszen Song, February 1997; 162418 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Nintendo Week Book, 1999; 162415 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Guys and Dolls, 1999; 162420 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Subseries VI: Scrapbooks, 162421
    - 1999-2000, 162422 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Subseries VII: Slides, 162423
    - October 1987, 162424 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - March 1992, 162425 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - O-Week, 1997; 162426 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - O-Week, c. 1998; 162427 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - n.d., 162428 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Subseries VIII: Photographs, 162429
    - Portrait of Harry Clay Hanszen, 1950; 162430 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Student Life, 1960s; 162431 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Students, 1980s; 162432 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - New Students (1 of 2), 1980s-2000s; 162433 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - New Students (2 of 2), 1980s-2000s; 162434 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - College Night, 1996; 162435 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Beer Bike, 1996; 162436 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Beer Bike, 1997; 162437 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Nintendo Week (1 of 3), 1999; 162438 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Nintendo Week (2 of 3), 1999; 162439 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Nintendo Week (3 of 3), 1999; 162440 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Flag football/Powderpuff, September 1999-October 1999; 162441 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Graduation, 1990s; 162442 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Student Life (1 of 2), 1990s-2000s; 162443 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Student Life (2 of 2), 1990s-2000s; 162444 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Bowling, 2000; 162445 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Beer Bike, 2002; 162446 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Graduation, 2002-2003; 162447 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Alternative Spring Break, March 2004; 162448 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Graduation, 2000s; 162449 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Students, 2000s; 162450 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Buildings, n.d.; 162451 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Subseries IX: Audio/Visual, 162452
    - Rice Philharmonics Hanszen Concert (DVD), March 3, 2005; 162453 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - La Cage Aux Folles (DVD), November 2005; 162454 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Series IV: Hanszen records, 1969-2012, 163390
  - Subseries I: Documents, 163391
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Library Committee, 1969; 163401 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - College Cabinet members, 1969-1993; 163396 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - On-Campus housing, 1975; 163399 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Animal policy, 1976; 163394 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - President's Honor Roll, 1985-2004; 163400 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - College anniversary, 1991; 163395 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Constitutional Revision Committee, 1991; 163397 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Freshman football orientation, 1992; 163398 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Subseries II: Photographs, 163392
    - 1991-1996 (1 of 2), 163402 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - 1991-1996 (2 of 2), 163403 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Campanile, 1995; 163404 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook, 1996/1997; 163405 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - 2000s, 163406 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Associates, 2000s; 163407 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - 2002, 163408 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - 2003, 163409 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - 2006, 163410 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - 2007, 163411 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - 2008, 163412 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - 2009, 163413 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 2010, 163414 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 2011, 163415 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 2012, 163416 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Subseries III: Artwork, 163393
    - Pharo-Week drawings by Courtney Svatek, 2010; 163417 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Superhero-Week drawing, 2000; 163418 (Map-drawer 148, Item 12)
      General Note
      Rice University Architectural drawings, oversize manuscript material, maps and photographs, Part 3 of 3 (UA 226-3)
  - Subseries IV: Audio/Visual, 163477
    - O-Week book and documents (CD and Zip Disk), 1996, 1997; 163483 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - O-Week book and documents (CD and Zip Disk), 1996; 163484 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - O-Week book and documents (CD and Zip Disk), 1997; 163485 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - O-Week book and documents (CD and Zip Disk), 1998; 163488 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - O-Week book and documents (CD and Zip Disk), 1999; 163491 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - O-Week book and documents (CD and Zip Disk), 2000; 163492 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Photographs (CD), 2009; 163495 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Series V: Hanszen records, 1957-2012, 172119
  - Subseries I: Government, 172120
    - Committee on Freshman Guidance, 1957; 172121 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Liquor regulations, 1964; 172122 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Regulations Governing Student Organizations and Student Social Functions, 1964; 172123 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Establishment of Residential College Offices, 1966; 172124 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Open House Policy, 1967; 172125 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Task Force on Colleges, 1975; 172126 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Rules and Regulations, 1972; 172128 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Judicial Code, 1978; 172127 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Constitution, 1981; 172129 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - By-laws, 1981; 172130 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Code of Judicial Procedure, 1983; 172132 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Government Guide, 1985; 172134 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Constitution and By-laws, 1988; 172135 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Judicial Code, 1988; 172136 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Fundraising, 1991; 172138 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Treasurer's Guide, 1991; 172139 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Constitution, 1996; 172140 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Election Code, 1997; 172142 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Bylaws, 1998; 172143 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Judicial Code, 1998; 172144 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Election blurb, b.d.; 172145 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Procedure for Establishment of Residential Colleges, n.d.; 172146 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Subseries II: Masters, 172147
    - College Master Plans, 1965; 172148 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 10th Anniversary of Hanszen speech by William H. Masterson, May 3, 1966; 172149 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - The Rice Daily Thresher - Coverage of Masterson Crisis, February 1969; 172150 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Masterson, William H. Quote, n.d.; 172151 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Subseries III: Minutes and Agenda, 172157
    - Cabinet Minutes and Agenda - includes proofs and notes, 1998/1999; 172153 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Cabinet, 2006/2007; 172154 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Cabinet Minutes, 2006/2007; 172156 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Cabinet Minutes, 2007/2008; 172159 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Cabinet Minutes, 2008/2009; 172160 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Cabinet Minutes, 2009/2010; 172161 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Cabinet Minutes, 2010/2011; 172163 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Subseries IV: O-Week, 172165
    - Handbook, 1969; 172167 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Handbook, 1970; 172168 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Handbook, 1983; 172170 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Handbook, 1986; 172171 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - PicassO Week Book, 1994; 172172 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Green Eggs and Hanszen O-Week Book, 1995; 172173 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Apollo Week Book, 1996; 172174 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Fred, Wilma, and Dino-Week Book, 1997; 172175 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Nintendo Week Book, 1999; 172176 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Super Mario Week Book, 2000; 172177 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Snoopy and Co. Week Book, 2002; 172178 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - O-Week Planning (CD), 2004; 172179 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - OWeek's 11 Book, 2004; 172180 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Lego-Week Book, 2005; 172181 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Formidable Foe Week Book, 2006; 172182 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - CheeriO-Week Book, 2008; 172183 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - AficionadO-Week Book, 2009; 172184 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - PharaO-Week Book (2 DVDs) (2 Books), 2010; 172185 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Zero to HerO-Week Book, 2011; 172186 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Apocalypto Week Book, 2012; 172187 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Subseries V: Publications, 172188
    - Associates Newsletter, Spring 2006; 172189 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Hanszen College: a History by Coco Owens and Ross Goldberg, 2012; 172190 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Hanszen History, 1992, n.d.; 172191 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - The Hanszen Voice, 1969-1971; 172192 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings, 1957-1980s; 172193 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - The Tower, 1974; 172194 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Subseries VI: Student Life, 172195
    - Alumni Brunch, 1998; 172196 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Fall Associates Night, n.d.; 172197 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Hanszen Musical Program, ca. 1965; 172198 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Masterson Room, 1983-1984; 172199 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Theater, 1993; 173227 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Subseries VII: Photographs, 172200
    - Beer Bike, 1950s-1980s; 172201 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Cabinet, 1958, 1962-1963; 172202 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Events, 1957-1980s; 172203 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Masters and RAs, 1950s-1960s; 172204 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Sports, 1966, n.d.; 172205 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Student Life, 1950s-1980s; 172206 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Theater, 1950s-1980s; 172207 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Series VI: Hanszen records, 1990-2013, 174915
  - Alcohol, 1993; 174936 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Alumni, 1991; 174937 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Budget, 1993/1994; 174938 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Budget, 1994/1995; 174939 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1996/1997; 174940 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1997/1998; 174941 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Budget, 1998/1999; 174942 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1990s; 174943 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Budget, 1990s; 174944 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Budget, 2000/2001; 174946 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 2002/2003; 174947 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Committees, 2002; 174948 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Constitution, 1990s; 174949 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Equipment, 1997; 174950 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - O-Week (photograph), 2010; 174951 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Senior Committee Budget, 1995; 174952 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Service Points, 2003/2004; 174953 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Theater, 2001-2002; 174954 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Theater, 2013; 174955 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Treasurer's Handbook, 2000/2001; 174956 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - CDs (15), 2003-2013; 174957 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    Items contained on these 15 CDs have been copied and placed on the USB in Box 20, Folder 13.
  - Subseries A: USB, 174916
    - O-Week, 2003; 174917 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 1)
    - O-Week, 2004; 174918 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 2)
    - O-Week, 2005; 174919 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 3)
    - Student Life, 2005-2006; 174920 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 4)
    - Graduation, 2006; 174921 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 5)
    - O-Week, 2006; 174922 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 6)
    - Student Life, Spring 2007; 174923 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 7)
    - O-Week, 2007; 174924 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 8)
    - Student Life, Fall 2007; 174925 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 9)
    - Student Life, Spring 2008; 174926 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 10)
    - O-Week, 2008; 174927 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 11)
    - Student Life, Fall 2008; 174928 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 12)
    - Student Life, Fall 2009; 174929 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 13)
    - Student Life, Fall 2010; 174930 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 14)
    - O-Week, 2011; 174931 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 15)
    - Student Life, Fall 2011; 174932 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 16)
    - Student Life, 2012-2013; 174933 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 17)
    - H-Team (Hanszen Adult Team), 2009-2012, n.d.; 174934 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 18)
    - Historical Images, 2005, 2007, n.d.; 174935 (Box 20, Folder 13, Subfolder 19)
  - First Hanszen Sweatshirt, 1990; 174958 (Box 21, Item 1)
    Detailed description of the sweatshirt's history is included in the box.
- Series VII: Hanszen records, 1988-2015, 181119
  - Subseries A: Documents, 181123
    - Bravo, Emma, 2014; 181120 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Calendar, 2014/2015; 181121 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Hanszen Happenings, Spring 2014; 181122 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Subseries B: Apparel, 181124
    - Beer Bike, 1988; 181125 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike (1 gray and 1 blue), 1990; 181126 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike (1 blue and 1 yellow), 1991; 181128 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike Sweep, 1991; 181129 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike, 1992; 181130 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike, 1993; 181132 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike, 1994; 181133 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike, 1998; 181134 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike, 1999; 181135 (Box 22)
    - Beer Bike, n.d.; 181137 (Box 22)
    - O-Week (1 green and 1 white), 1989; 181138 (Box 22)
    - O-Week Nintendo Week, 1999; 183471 (Box 22)
    - Graduation stoles, n.d. (Box 22)
    - Hanszen College blanket, n.d. (Box 22)
- Series VIII: Hanszen records, 1963-2015
  - Chorus Music, ca. 1963 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Student Life photographs, 2010-2012 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series A: Digital Archive
    These items were downloaded from the Hanszen College Digital Archive Google Drive, converted to pdf files, saved to an internal server, and printed. The digital files will be kept until June 2017. After that, the digital files will be deleted, but the physical files will remain in the collection.
    - Sub-Sub-Series 1: Caroline Gutierrez, 2013-2014
      - Beer Bike (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Budget (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Cabinet Agendas (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Constitution (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Pre-Cabinet Agendas and Minutes (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - President (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - President Caroline Gutierrez files
    - Sub-Sub-Series 2: T.J. Patel, 2014-2015
      - Cabinet (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Constitution (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - President (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Secretaries (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - President T.J. Patel files